Shogakukan
Sản xuất
Studio Pierrot
Shogakukan Productions
OV Planning
Rumiko Takahashi
Rumic
World
Đây là một câu truyện giả tưởng!!
Cô gái siêu phàm
Hắn tè ra quần.
Kinh vãi!
Nhân viên của Cục Vận chuyển Jubei!
Tôi sẽ bắt anh vì tội buôn lậu ma tuý!
Cô làm tốt lắm, Maris!
Cứ để tôi lo, Murphy.
Hoan hô, được nghỉ phép rồi!
Maris, cô chưa mặc bộ kháng lực đấy!
Chết!
Ma-Maris!
Thiếu uý Maris, đây đã là chiếc thứ ba rồi đấy.
Nhưng mà Đại tá, bộ ngài
không thấy đây là lỗi của ngài,
khi đưa cho tôi phi thuyền Trái Đất sao?
Vì tôi mạnh gấp 6 lần người Trái Đất lận mà.
Nhưng cô vẫn phải bồi thường thiệt hại.
Rõ rồi chứ?
Cô hiểu chứ, Thiếu uý Maris?
Hành tinh Oween
Ta sẽ trễ mất!
Mấy chiếc vé đến buổi biểu diễn mà ta phải
vất vả để có được sẽ uỏng phí mất.
Nên lẹ lên chú ơi!
Bên này~
"Chữ trên lá cờ: Taxi Người"
Có vẻ như bác muốn đi Taxi Người nhỉ?
Đúng không?
K-Không, ưm, tôi...
Đừng có chọc tức cổ. Cô ta là
người Thanatos tàn bạo đấy.
Ế?! Cái hành tinh Thanatos bị nổ tung sao?
Bác muốn đi Taxi người, đúng không?
Ơ... Vâng.
Woo mitsumeteru
Woo, nhìn chằm chằm.
Woo sasayaki wa
Woo, thì thầm.
Doa o aketara aitsu wa SEXY
Em mở cửa ra, và anh ấy thật Sexy làm sao.
Furimuki zama ni inai
Khi ngoảnh mặt lại nhìn thì anh đã biến mất rồi.
Woo doko made mo
Woo, dù có là ở đâu đi nữa.
Woo tsuzuiteru
Woo, cứ kéo dài mãi.
Namiuchigiwa de aitsu wa paradaisu
Ở trên bãi biển,
anh chính là thiên đường của em.
Mabataki sureba inai
Vừa chớp mắt thôi thì anh đã biến mất rồi.
Fushigina made no Rumic World
Thế giới Rumic nhiệm màu.
Koko wa uwasa no Long Long Beach?
Đây có phải là Bãi biển Dài Dằng dặc
mà người ta đồn đại.
Nakanaide
Đừng khóc mà.
Terenaide
Đừng xấu hổ thế chứ.
Hohoemeba kochira wa yukaina kiatsu haichizu
Cười lên rồi bạn sẽ thấy đây là
một tấm bản đồ khí áp dễ chịu.
Buin! Buin! Buin!
Ben! Bèn! Ben!
Kono mama
Hãy cứ tiếp tục.
Ki no mama
Làm những gì trái tim ta mách bảo.
Uchuu ni ukabu yuu wakuwaku wakuwaku sei
Như một ngôi sao năng động trôi nổi trong vũ trụ.
It's so hot!
Dammit!
We finally got a vacation, and I still have to work!
Quit complaining. I look like an idiot walking next to you.
Too expensive?
What are you saying?!
Renting a car would have been twice as much!
Thanatos. Remember, Thanatos!
Right, right.
The breeze from 5,000
credits feels so cool!
Okay, let's find our next victim.
No matter how often I do it,
this job is embarrassing.
Being poor is to blame!
Huh?
Ouch!
Hey!
Oh no, I need to go to the bathroom!
Help, I can't get free!
I can't hold it any longer!
Maris, you have a long distance phone call from Planet Ahoya.
Huh?
Hurry up!
Okay.
Be right there.
They said it was important.
Dad, come here. It's little Maris.
Maris, could you lend us some money?
I knew it.
Well, you see,
we're at the supermarket right now,
and your father's restraints broke.
See! Look!
See this?
He was drunk, so he didn't realize it.
But when he leaned on the shelf... see what happened?
And so?
Someone better pay for the damages, or I'm calling the police!
Please, Maris.
You're the only one we can ask.
What am I supposed to do?
If only we weren't from Thanatos.
You promised not to say that, Mother!
But... Maris...
Take a good look.
Burn it into your memories.
Our home world.
This is the end of our mother planet, Thanatos!
I understand.
I'll get a payday advance and send whatever I can.
Thank you, Maris.
Sorry to bother you all the time.
But...
What, Maris?
Next time, buy better restraints.
No more bargains from festival booths, like last time!
Also, no more mail order trash, either!
Okay, Maris.
Bye.
Goodbye!
Maris!
So Lieutenant Maris,
how do you like your new ship?
How do I like it?
Well, it's a piece of junk.
It's a secondhand '62 Pippopotamus!
Interstellar Consumer rates it a Worst Buy.
That explains the scowl on your face.
Look who's talking.
Did you enjoy your vacation?
Shut up! Mind your own business.
I had to work the whole time.
Oh, I see. That explains your scowl.
Look who's talking!
Did you enjoy your vacation?
Hey, Colonel...
Oh yes, I've got you covered for your payday advance and the hotel damages.
Th-Thanks.
Have you forgotten how I rescued you from your last job?
Isn't the Space Patrol better than the cruel world of pro wrestling?
My debt just got bigger.
Well, about your next mission...
Okay, tell me already.
The son of a high official
has been kidnapped.
The crooks are holed up on Planet Moroi.
They want a huge ransom.
A kidnapping?
The kidnappers sent us these pictures of their victim.
He's cheerful.
Um... These were taken after
he was kidnapped, right?
Strangely happy, isn't he?
That's probably because his father is a billionaire.
A billionaire?
He's Koganemaru,
son of Matsushita Sanchi.
Matsushita?!
He's the richest person in the galaxy!
Well, I wish you good luck!
Please wait for me, Koganemaru.
I'm coming to rescue you.
What are you thinking, Maris?
Didn't you hear, Murphy?
He's the son of a billionaire!
You saved my life.
Please marry me.
Yup.
My beloved Maris.
I slave away for a pitiful salary.
I do part-time jobs on vacations.
Dad's an alcoholic,
and Mom's an airhead!
And I have to wear these stupid restraints because of my power!
My youth is...
wasting away!
It's just a small crack.
Nothing to worry about.
If I complete this mission successfully,
I can say goodbye to this miserable life!
Hold on, my prince!
I'm sorry, but we're not
meant for each other.
We come from two different worlds.
I want a graceful girl,
not some barbarian from Thanatos!
You're just greedy pigs with fat thighs!
It would never work.
This isn't really what I prefer.
You bastard! Stop using that stupid power!
Hành tinh Moroi
The enemy ship approaches.
What's the meaning of this, Sue?
Didn't I tell you to write "Do not contact the police" in the ransom letter?
I bet the Space Patrol's
Special Police interfered.
Special Police, huh?
Fascinating.
Let's kill the hostage, as a warning.
Don't be a fool!
We should kill the police instead.
If we keep the hostage alive, we can keep on asking for ransom money.
We need to keep on making money,
or we'll never be able to buy a new fortress!
Yeah, this thing's ancient.
Earth-made bases are
cheap pieces of junk.
It's been five years since I left my pathetic home on Bakan.
Now, a chance to make it big time has arrived.
If only I was rich,
I'd finally be free from
these stupid restraints!
Death to the Special Police!
Being poor is to blame!
Attack, Sue!
Roger!
Dammit!
I wish you luck.
I'll save you, my prince.
What's that?
Damn, they're on to me.
Prepare to die, Special Police operative!
Vampire Maris!
Zombie Sue!
You're still alive, Maris?
I wondered about you and your big debt.
Imagine, you sank so low as to join the Special Police.
Right back at ya! You've stooped so low as to become a kidnapper, huh?
The Special Police
are pawns that specialize in dangerous missions.
You do the Patrol's dirty work, right?
Am I wrong?
What was that?!
You pawn! Pawn! Pawn!
Sh-Shut up, you criminal!
Damn you, Zombie Sue!
I won't lose!
If I lose now, I'll always be poor!
Bitch!
I'm behind her!
Die, kidnapper!
Gotcha!
Bye bye, Vampire Maris.
Forever.
I can't die now!
I trashed another ship.
When dawn arrives
I fall asleep
In a world
So strange to me
Everywhere I turn
I only see waves of sand
I long for those days
When I
Was together
With you
Please return the dream
That I entrusted
To you long ago
Our memories are like an oasis
A green lullaby
Run hand in hand through the meadow
You and I will be together forever
Water?
Water.
Water!
Do you feel better now?
This is no time for jokes, you bastard!
I've found the survivors.
Going in to rescue them now. Over.
What now?
We're penniless.
Do you want us to die in this rundown hick town?
Shut up!
There it is!
There! There!
I've found a job!
What? You did?
Look, over there!
Now we can buy food!
It figures. Even out here, it was just a passing fad.
So you survived, Lieutenant Maris.
I'm up here.
Colonel!
Surprising to see you here!
I lost contact and decided to investigate.
Return to HQ immediately and await new orders!
Hành tinh Ahoya · Trụ sở Cảnh sát Đặc nhiệm
Four ships, advance pay,
new restraints, etc.
A 30-year loan at 100,000 credits a month,
plus your bonus of 30,000 credits.
Well, that should cover everything.
That leaves nothing for me!
Your new ship is ready.
Now rescue that hostage!
Good luck, Lieutenant Maris.
For crying out loud!
What does he expect me to do with a huge cockpit like this?
Wait for me, my prince.
Let's go, Murphy.
Roger.
Wait, Murphy. It's an emergency call.
I'm so sorry, Maris, but we need to borrow some more money.
We're at the restraint store.
You can tell, right?
And?
Your father stopped
for a few teensy drinks.
I had the wallet,
but I looked away for a second. I'm sick and tired of this-
Father, Mother...
Hold on.
I'll get rich and buy you a planet
where you won't need restraints.
Murphy! Let's go!
We're here, we're here!
Maris, doesn't this seem suspicious?
Isn't it odd that we could infiltrate this place so easily?
I'll save you soon, my prince!
I'm yours! I'm yours!
We're right in front of their base!
I'm all yours. Now, please give me some money!
Huh? Did you say something?
Don't talk to me!
I'm contemplating whether I should ever say anything serious to you again!
Maris, I've always loved you!
Stop acting like an idiot
at a time like this!
Welcome to Moroi,
Miss Special Police.
Who are you?
My welcoming committee
is waiting outside.
Oh, don't do anything stupid, or the hostage will die.
Throw down your weapons
and come out.
Put up your hands.
Hurry up!
Half the landing gear
is completely ruined.
Big...
Wh-What's this?
A remote-control lock.
You can't remove your restraints.
Now, should we go?
Wow! A prefab Earth base.
Looks flimsy.
Ancient.
Don't underestimate it.
It's efficient.
Yeah, right.
Hurry up and go inside!
I see. An execution, huh?
Yeah, and I have the perfect method.
I'll kill her so cruelly that
the Space Police will get scared.
Want to watch?
I have no need to watch a hawk devour an insignificant baby sparrow.
If you say so.
Good luck.
It seems your last hope has been snuffed out, Koganemaru.
Here's your dinner, Koganemaru!
You don't look well.
What do you plan to do with me in a place like this?
With restraints on, a Thanatosian is as weak as an Earthling.
I'm only strength 3.
Normally, I could never
beat a Thanatosian.
Maris.
Keep in mind that if you interfere, not even your bones will remain.
It's no use. You need the remote control I'm holding to remove it.
Dammit!
Maris!
I'm going to kill you slowly.
How dirty! And you call
yourself a human?!
Being poor is to blame!
Here I come!
Don't use being poor as an excuse!
I'm poor too, you know!
Dammit!
I gotta hurry over to the ropes.
Time out! Time out!
Maris...
Dammit!
You bitch.
Which one's real? Which one's real?
Which one's real?
It's you.
Maris!
It's the remote control.
I can't reach it!
She'll be dead before you can get it.
A bit more. A bit more.
Oh, dammit!
Why, you...
It fell! It fell down!
Almost...
Got it!
I did it!
They came off!
Wh-What are you doing?
Hey, wait!
How about this!
Stop it! Don't break it. Please!
Stop! Please, stop!
Shut up!
Hold it!
You're the boss of the kidnappers!
Indeed.
Money...
I mean, give back the hostage!
I can't do that.
We'll die with our fortress.
I'm taking you and the hostage with us!
You can stop that now.
I've already given up.
But why?
She wrecked my base!
What am I supposed to do now?!
Are you sure you really want to stop?
How boring.
Koganemaru!
Are you surprised? Miss Specto... uh...
Special polito... no...
It's "police."
Oh, Miss Police.
What's going on?
You two were in on it together?
No.
I really kidnapped him, but...
I was bored, so I decided to try being a crime lord.
Only a billionaire's son
could be so bold.
Good job. You did great.
Your rescue went perfectly,
Miss Special... uh...
Police officer Maris.
That's right.
I will... I will...
My home world is such a poor planet.
I hated being poor,
so I wanted to run away.
I built this fortress as my last hope.
Koganemaru...
Koganemaru, let's go back to your father.
I even wore those stupid restraints to protect my beautiful base.
Don't cry, okay?
Look, we can just make another one.
I'll pay for it.
Sue...
Don't you hate me?
Why? It was fun.
Don't cry. You'll ruin your pretty face.
Let's get married, Sue.
What?!
Hey, Lieutenant Maris!
What about your mission?
Stay still!
Why you bastard!
If you break this one, it'll be your fifth ship!
Calm down!
Geez!
Hey!
My goodness!
Lieutenant Maris!
Being poor is to blame!
Hết
mune no haato wa doku kinoko
Your heart is like a poisoned mushroom.
shibana ga tonda enerugii
Sparks fly out, it's energy!
umaretsuite no amazonesu
You're a natural born Amazoness!
fijikaru biito sora wo yuku
The physical beat soars through the sky!
konoyo ha maane manee
This world is all about money, I'd say.
tokimeku genkin ne
Money affects everything today.
shiawase naraba te wo
So if you're happy,
tatakou
clap your hands.
binbo ranbo
Poverty! Violence!
koi wa chikara
Love is power.
binbo shinbo
Poverty! Patience!
tsukame Big Success
Take it all. Big success!
ten to jigoku no wakaremichi
Heaven and Hell are divided by a road of money!
kane ga nararu tamanokoshi
Coins jingle jingle, a merry sound.
Marry for money!
pinchi mo sou yo pinhane de
In a pinch, some money would be as good.
chansu ni dansu odocchae
It's a chance to dance, I know you'll take it!
otoko ha maane manee
All men are boys with money, I'd say.
body te ima kurejitto
Their bodies gleam.
Credit charged, you know!
shitataka wagamamana sekushii pawaa
Super greedy with incredible sexy power!
binbo ranbo
Poverty! Violence!
mirai wa soka sa
The future will be like that!
binbo shinbo
Poverty! Patience!
moero Good Success
Fiery good success!
konoyo wa maane manee
This world is all about money, I'd say.
mihatenu yume gokochi
It's easy living in a broken dream,
uchuu no anettai
deep in the jungle of a cosmic sea.
uuman pawaa
Woman power!
binbo ranbo
Poverty! Violence!
koi wa chikara
Love is power!
binbo shinbo
Poverty! Patience!
tsukame Big Success
Take it all. Big success!